<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Cerbervs</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Cerbervs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 12:45:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Moon</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/my-moon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 12:45:29 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/my-moon/</guid>
      <description>My Moon If I am the sea, and you are my Moon,&#xA;then I shall flow and ebb,&#xA;and swell and crash,&#xA;against the cliffs to stretch my height.&#xA;If I am the sea, all purple and blue&#xA;with blacks and whites, all roiling in my depths,&#xA;then I shall concentrate all my might,&#xA;and reach toward you.&#xA;If I am the sea, no length shall stop me,&#xA;no great ceiling of the sky,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Will Carry You as Atlas Carries the Sky (Reprise)</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/atlas-sky-reprise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 12:41:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/atlas-sky-reprise/</guid>
      <description>I Will Carry You as Atlas Carries the Sky (Reprise) We will be the salt of the earth at the end of days.&#xA;Returned from dust, to dust.&#xA;Made from ash, molded by fire, and flame.&#xA;We came into this world screaming, and we will not leave quietly, not without struggle.&#xA;We will have stood tall at times, we will have crawled a time a time or two,&#xA;and our hands and feet will be calloused.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If You&#39;d Care to Talk</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/if-youd-care-to-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 12:40:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/if-youd-care-to-talk/</guid>
      <description>If You&amp;rsquo;d Care to Talk Please use my name when you address me.&#xA;I will hear all the words you speak, again, when the time comes to lay my head down.&#xA;It sounds so delicate, wrapped gently in your voice.&#xA;I want to clutch it in my head, black and silken, stitched just so around the edges of the way you call me.&#xA;I want it to echo through me, bursting like claps of thunder, and calmly like the pitter-patter of soft rains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thin or Thinning Out</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/thin-or-thinning-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 12:17:50 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/thin-or-thinning-out/</guid>
      <description>Thin. Or, Thinning Out I&amp;rsquo;ve been feeling thin lately&#xA;or&#xA;thinning out, I&amp;rsquo;m not sure. Either way, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t hurt like I thought it would.&#xA;It seems I&amp;rsquo;m made of paper, been left in the rain, edges fraying, with each drop another tiny fragment of me gone.&#xA;The rain is cool and soft - pleasant - altogether not a bad day to be thin. Gentle, even though abrasive.&#xA;But how thin can one get before they&amp;rsquo;re gone completely, every last bit washed away in the downpour.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clutch</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/clutch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 12:11:12 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/clutch/</guid>
      <description>Clutch The addict will drink the sea until it becomes him.&#xA;And just so, I would let you drown me in your darkest depths.&#xA;Pull me under and clutch me in your currents, embraced for what would end as eternity.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;d gladly heave the air from my lungs to make room for more of you.&#xA;Pour the contents of my visceral cavity out so you can fill my chest for the first time since my birth.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
