<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cerbervs</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/poems/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cerbervs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© [Cerbervs](https://github.com/cerbervs) 2024-Present</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 10:04:38 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/poems/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Clutch</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/poems/clutch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 12:11:12 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/poems/clutch/</guid>
      <description>The addict will drink the sea until it becomes him.&#xA;And just so, I would let you drown me in your darkest depths.&#xA;Pull me under and clutch me in your currents, embraced for what would end as eternity.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;d gladly heave the air from my lungs to make room for more of you.&#xA;Pour the contents of my visceral cavity out so you can fill my chest for the first time since my birth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demagogue</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/poems/demagogue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 13:03:38 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/poems/demagogue/</guid>
      <description>I want you to fall for me, as if you slipped at the top of ten flights of stairs.&#xA;Like you tried to grab the rungs for the banister, desperately clutched at them, only to realize they are slick with something and you can&amp;rsquo;t get a grip.&#xA;Sliding down the stairs, wooden, no carpeting, just hard edges to knock the breath from your body.&#xA;Steep as they are, you ended up going head over heels, tumbling down, elbows thrown into walls, fingernails dug into any surface where they could find purchase.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Will Carry You as Atlas Carries the Sky (Reprise)</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/poems/atlas-sky-reprise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 12:41:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/poems/atlas-sky-reprise/</guid>
      <description>We will be the salt of the earth at the end of days.&#xA;Returned from dust, to dust.&#xA;Made from ash, molded by fire, and flame.&#xA;We came into this world screaming, and we will not leave quietly, not without struggle.&#xA;We will have stood tall at times, we will have crawled a time a time or two,&#xA;and our hands and feet will be calloused. Sometimes carrying each other, sometimes dragged by the little clothing we have left.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If You&#39;d Care to Talk</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/poems/if-youd-care-to-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 12:40:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/poems/if-youd-care-to-talk/</guid>
      <description>Please use my name when you address me.&#xA;I will hear all the words you speak, again, when the time comes to lay my head down.&#xA;It sounds so delicate, wrapped gently in your voice.&#xA;I want to clutch it in my head, black and silken, stitched just so around the edges of the way you call me.&#xA;I want it to echo through me, bursting like claps of thunder, and calmly like the pitter-patter of soft rains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week One</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/poems/week-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 09:57:04 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/poems/week-one/</guid>
      <description>Take the chip off your shoulder, my dear,&#xA;your frame looks fairer without it.&#xA;You&amp;rsquo;ve been choking up, lately, I can hear the lies in the back of your throat, they make an awful sound.&#xA;I know it&amp;rsquo;s hard to be honest, I really do.&#xA;I struggle myself sometimes, find my tongue tied into odd shapes to accomdate the yarns I&amp;rsquo;ve spun.&#xA;But please, please god tell me what is really at the bottom of this gaping wound, proud flesh, gnarled and raw.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week Two</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/poems/week-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 10:00:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/poems/week-two/</guid>
      <description>Tired like a bird dog, all but spent, just enough of himself left to trudge the mile or so home.&#xA;Ready to collapse as soon as the threshold has been crossed, bed not far from the door of this tiny abode.&#xA;A hard day&amp;rsquo;s work done, sun from the window glinting off the hairs laid flat across his back; hackles no longer raised at the fleeting thought of some tasty morsel, falling fast from the sky.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Time We Lost</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/poems/this-time-we-lost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 10:04:38 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/poems/this-time-we-lost/</guid>
      <description>So everyone has left, I am here alone,&#xA;for a week, give or take.&#xA;And this weight I&amp;rsquo;ve been feeling on my shoulders,&#xA;it&amp;rsquo;s on my chest now too.&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s getting real heavy, it&amp;rsquo;s starting to hurt real bad.&#xA;Felt like I was scraping by, up there, with you.&#xA;And now I&amp;rsquo;m home again, and I fucking hate that I have to be here.&#xA;But there is no other way, just the road in front of me as I slip further from you.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Daydream of You</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/poems/a-daydream-of-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 15:51:05 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/poems/a-daydream-of-you/</guid>
      <description>As I awoke, glistening white, brittle little flakes were cascading down from a pitchy sky.&#xA;No star adorning the upper reaches of my vision, my eyes were bleary.&#xA;I had found myself in unfamiliar territory again.&#xA;I stood, knees creaking, it being cold around me, of course they would.&#xA;Still sickened from the day that lead me there, to that otherworldly street, empty and silent.&#xA;I looked up from my scuffed boots, and lo!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Limbo</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/poems/limbo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 15:48:01 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/poems/limbo/</guid>
      <description>As this day draws to a sweltering close,&#xA;I am afforded a look at the length of time we have occupied&#xA;together.&#xA;It seems far longer than it was and far shorter than it ever could have been.&#xA;Caught in some sort of limbo, we floated,&#xA;not daring to look down, not striving to reach up.&#xA;Gorging ourselves on the fruits we found on the underside of branches, tickling the tops of our heads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stuck</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/poems/stuck/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 14:36:18 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/poems/stuck/</guid>
      <description>Here I am, between my rock and a hard place.&#xA;I cannot even struggle to free myself.&#xA;This weight won&amp;rsquo;t let up.&#xA;It struck me, free falling from somewhere I do not know.&#xA;And pinned me here.&#xA;This boulder is so damn heavy.&#xA;Not a single budge, no nanometer of movement, for all that I squirm.&#xA;I can barely breathe.&#xA;This is crushing me.&#xA;I keep thinking about what it would be like to be free again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maybe Then I Will Find My Peace</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/poems/maybe-then-i-will-find-my-peace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 13:08:48 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/poems/maybe-then-i-will-find-my-peace/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t think this fire will ever truly burn out.&#xA;The coals will be banked, yes, but smolder forever.&#xA;There&amp;rsquo;s no letting this go completely. No way to forget you.&#xA;And that&amp;rsquo;s okay, I think. It&amp;rsquo;s a quiet longing that doesn&amp;rsquo;t need to be acknowledged.&#xA;One that I don&amp;rsquo;t think about until I&amp;rsquo;m awake in the middle of the night. Bolt upright in bed.&#xA;Sitting next to her, your replacement. Cold sweat dripping in bullets down my brow, the center of my back, along my spine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penny for Your Thoughts</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/poems/penny-for-your-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 12:54:56 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/poems/penny-for-your-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>Penny for your thoughts, love.&#xA;Let&amp;rsquo;s spill our guts out across the floor, wielding short blades of blood-blackened steel.&#xA;Ancient and sharp, carried between our teeth.&#xA;Try to shove the innards back into each other, no instructions, just instinct.&#xA;Let&amp;rsquo;s count how many stitches it takes to keep everything inside. Just enough thread to pull the ragged bits of skin together over our fragile bones and soft bits.&#xA;Penny for your thoughts, love, do I look pretty spread out across the room, reddened and empty?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empty, Not Abandoned</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/poems/empty-not-abandoned/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 12:52:38 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/poems/empty-not-abandoned/</guid>
      <description>I am an empty house, not abandoned.&#xA;But within there is no comfort.&#xA;Put on display to so many potential buyers, or takers, as it is.&#xA;One after another looking over my cracks, my broken mirrors.&#xA;Turning away from the chandelier, no longer in working order, bulbs and crystal fled their high perch long ago.&#xA;Time and time again, shaking heads, moving on.&#xA;And yet here you are.&#xA;You look at me with such care in those endless eyes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>but it feels just fine</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/poems/but-it-feels-just-fine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 12:50:01 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/poems/but-it-feels-just-fine/</guid>
      <description>So it begins. Here, now, in this car. Window rolled down.&#xA;Cold air brushing my cheeks with it&amp;rsquo;s snowy fingers.&#xA;But it feels just fine.&#xA;Noise. Endless noise cascading through the cracks in the doors. Seeping through the windshield, onto the seats.&#xA;The passenger seat is empty. As it most often is now.&#xA;But it feels just fine.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;ve been yearning for touch. I&amp;rsquo;ve been pining for the familiar scent of skin climbing up my nose, into my brain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Moon</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/poems/my-moon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 12:45:29 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/poems/my-moon/</guid>
      <description>If I am the sea, and you are my Moon,&#xA;then I shall flow and ebb,&#xA;and swell and crash,&#xA;against the cliffs to stretch my height.&#xA;If I am the sea, all purple and blue&#xA;with blacks and whites, all roiling in my depths,&#xA;then I shall concentrate all my might,&#xA;and reach toward you.&#xA;If I am the sea, no length shall stop me,&#xA;no great ceiling of the sky,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thin or Thinning Out</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/poems/thin-or-thinning-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 12:17:50 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/poems/thin-or-thinning-out/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been feeling thin lately&#xA;or&#xA;thinning out, I&amp;rsquo;m not sure. Either way, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t hurt like I thought it would.&#xA;It seems I&amp;rsquo;m made of paper, been left in the rain, edges fraying, with each drop another tiny fragment of me gone.&#xA;The rain is cool and soft - pleasant - altogether not a bad day to be thin. Gentle, even though abrasive.&#xA;But how thin can one get before they&amp;rsquo;re gone completely, every last bit washed away in the downpour.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
